this lecture was look at voting schemed
这堂课是看投票计划的
a little more closely and the main
更紧密和主要
message of this segment will be that
该段的消息是
even very reasonable sounding voting
甚至听起来很合理的投票
schemes can run into problems and we'll
方案可能会遇到问题，我们将
do it by a series of examples we'll look
我们将通过一系列示例来做到这一点
at situation I'll ask you to pause the
在这种情况下，我会请您暂停
video and think about the situation and
视频并考虑情况
then we'll and to continue when you're
然后我们会继续，当您
ready so let's get let's get started
准备好了，让我们开始吧
let's start with the condos sake endorse
让我们从公寓的缘故开始
a condition which on the face of it is
从表面上看是
incontrovertible and consider the
坚不可摧，并考虑
following examples so here we are we
下面的例子，所以我们在这里
have a thousand agents and and here are
有一千个代理商，这是
their preferences so for example four
他们的偏好，例如四个
hundred and ninety nine of them prefer A
其中109个喜欢A
to B to C and so on for the others first
从B到C，以此类推。
question is not every voting situation
问题不是每个投票情况
has a converse a winner does this one
有一个交谈者获胜者做到这一点
have says good time for you to pause the
说了好时间让您暂停
video and think about it well the answer
视频并仔细考虑答案
is yes there is a conversation winner
是的，有一个对话的赢家
and it's B and why is that
是B，那是为什么
well let's look at their relative
好，让我们看看他们的亲戚
preference of B to a and the relevant
B对a的偏爱及相关
preference of B to C well we have here
B对C的偏爱我们在这里
that 500 and one of the agents prefer B
500和其中一位特工更喜欢B
to a and 502 of the agents prefer B to C
到a和502的代理商更喜欢B到C
so clearly B is a conversate winner
所以很明显B是一个对话的赢家
well that so where's the problem well
好，那么问题出在哪里
now think about the simplest sort of
现在考虑最简单的一种
voting we're familiar with plurality
投票，我们熟悉复数
voting everybody votes for their top
投票给所有人投票
candidate who would win the plurality
赢得多元化的候选人
voting here well again you could pause
再次在这里投票可以暂停
the video or in this case it's fairly
视频，或者在这种情况下，
straightforward right
直截了当的权利
clearly a would win it because 490
显然一个会赢，因为490
agents would vote for a and the next
代理商会投票给A和下一个
highest number would be C with 498 so
最高的数字将是C与498，所以
morality boating doesn't give you the
道德划船不会给你
candidate that on the face of it
表面上的候选人
is the clear should be the clear winner
是明确的应该是明确的赢家
what about voting plurality with
用...投票复数怎么办
elimination so this might take a little
消除，所以这可能需要一点时间
more time to think about so you might
有更多时间思考，所以您可能
want to pause the video here just for a
想要在这里暂停视频只是为了
second and now when you think about it
第二，现在当您考虑它时
you see that C would be the winner under
您会看到C将是下一个赢家
pure reality with in elimination and why
消除中的纯现实，为什么
is that well you'd first run a plurality
那是您首先要运行多个
and you'll see that B is the loser
你会看到B是失败者
so B would leave the competition if you
所以B如果你愿意离开比赛
wish and now it'll be head-to-head
希望，现在将是正面交锋
between CNA and in this case C would be
在CNA与C之间
the winner because 501 out of the
获胜者，因为501分
thousand agents prefer C to a so C would
成千上万的代理商更喜欢C而不是C
be the winner and so two voted teams
成为赢家，所以有两个投票小组
both of them on the face of it
他们俩都面对它
reasonable would give you different
合理会给你不同
answers and both answer is different
答案和两个答案都不同
from the criterion that on the face of
从面对的标准
it seems quite a safe criterion namely
看来相当安全的标准是
the cantos a foundation so here's
cantos基础，所以这里是
another example and let's think about
另一个例子，让我们考虑一下
what would happen in this case what
在这种情况下会发生什么
would happen under pure reality voting
将在纯现实投票下发生
well clearly under Florida voting a
很明显，在佛罗里达投票下
would win since I would get 35 votes and
会赢，因为我将获得35票，
the second highest would be B with 33
第二高的是33
what would happened under the board of
在董事会的领导下会发生什么
voting this takes a little more thinking
投票这需要更多的思考
and you might want to pause just for a
而您可能只想暂停一下
second the video but when you continue
第二个视频，但是当您继续时
by that time you'll quickly realize that
到那时你会很快意识到
again a would be the winner under border
再一次将是边界下的赢家
and clearly you have
显然你有
a B and C each appearing in each of the
B和C分别出现在每个
places one two or three with a appearing
放置一两个或三个出现
with the largest number of agents and
代理商数量最多
the higher locations so they would have
较高的位置，所以他们将有
the highest board account and would be
董事会最高帐户，并且
the one or two so this looks very good
一两个这样看起来很好
but now what happens if she drops out so
但是现在如果她退学了怎么办
C realizes that he has no no chance of
C意识到自己没有机会
winning the election and drops out now
赢得选举，现在退学
what would happen under the both
在这两种情况下会发生什么
plurality and border just you might want
您可能想要的复数和边框
to pause for a second the video and
暂停一秒钟的视频，
think about it and when you do you
考虑一下，什么时候做
realize that in both cases B would win
意识到在两种情况下B都会赢
and so here you have a candidate that
所以这里有一个候选人
has no chance of winning and is sole
没有获胜的机会，而且是唯一的
role if you wish is to change what
如果您希望改变的角色
otherwise would be the outcome of the
否则将是
elections here is another acuity of
这里的选举是
voting schemes and imagine that we're
投票计划并想象我们
doing terrorise elimination that is
做恐怖消除
we're going to take one candidate to
我们将带一名候选人参加
compare him to another take the winner
比较他和另一个获胜者
comparing to a third and so on and so
比较三分之一等等
forth so the order in which we compare
所以我们比较的顺序
the candidates we call that the agenda
我们称之为议程的候选人
so somebody needs to set the agenda we
所以有人需要设定议程
call that person the attenders agenda
将该人称为与会者议程
setter so imagine pairwise elimination
二传手，所以想像成对消除
with the order of comparison ABC in
与比较顺序ABC在
other words a would be compared to B and
换句话说a将与B进行比较
then B will be compared to C so who
那么B将与C相比较
would be the winner of this election a
将是这次选举的赢家
good time to pause the video and think
暂停视频并思考的好时机
about it and once you do you realize
关于它，一旦你意识到
that C would be the winner because when
C是赢家，因为当
a is compared to B well we have be
a与B相比较，我们已经
preferred to a by a majority of the
被大多数人偏爱
agents so a would be eliminated and then
代理，因此将被淘汰，然后
when the winner namely B is compared to
当获胜者即B与
C you'll see that C is preferred to B by
C，您会看到C比B更偏爱B
the majority of the agent and therefore
大多数代理商，因此
C will be the winner of this election
C将是这次选举的获胜者
with this ordering what happens with
按照这种顺序会发生什么
another ordering like ACB again you
再次像ACB一样订购
might want to pause the video and when
可能想暂停视频以及何时
we read by the time you resume will
我们会在您恢复简历时阅读
realize that this case B would be the
意识到这种情况B将是
winner and perhaps not surprisingly when
赢家，也许并不奇怪
you asked about the third ordering BCA
您询问了第三个订购BCA
you'll see that a would be the or the
您会看到a将是或
winner there and so it's a little
那里的赢家，所以有点
perhaps disconcerting that a the same
也许让我感到相同
voting scheme merely by deciding on the
仅通过决定投票方案
order in which you run it would lead to
您运行的顺序将导致
very different results and here is
非常不同的结果，这是
another example there are three agents
另一个例子有三个代理
and four candidates and the preferences
和四个候选人和偏好
are written up there now consider again
被写在那里，现在再考虑
pairwise elimination with the ABCD
与ABCD成对消除
ordering and what would you get again
订购，您还会得到什么
pause the video for a second think about
暂停视频再三思
it and realize that the winner would be
并意识到获胜者将是
d what about what about this case we're
d我们在这种情况下怎么样
not talking about different orderings
不谈论不同的顺序
we're talking about a given ordering and
我们在谈论给定的顺序，
an outcome but there's something a
结果，但有一些
little troubling about this outcome what
这个结果有点令人不安
is it pause the video think about it and
视频暂停了吗？
realize that the problem is that
意识到问题是
everyone prefers B to D here right so B
每个人都喜欢B比D好，所以B
is preferred to D here be referred to D
优先于D，这里称为D
here and be referred to D here and yet d
在这里，并在这里被称为D
this purrito dominated candidate wins
这个purrito主导的候选人获胜
something is wrong in this picture well
这幅画出了点问题
the goal here was not to give us the
目的不是要给我们
final answer what what is the right way
最后的答案是什么正确的方法
to vote in fact that is not well-defined
投票实际上定义不明确
the goal was to alert us to that the
目的是提醒我们
fact that a lot of reasonable sounding
事实很多合理
voting schemes can can be problematic
投票方案可能会有问题
and so with this note of caution
因此请注意
we'll finish this segment
我们将结束本段